Finding aid for the Henry Clay Frick Papers, Series II: Correspondence, 1882-1929, undated HCFF.1.2
The Frick Collection/Frick Art Reference Library Archives
- Creelman, Alice B. [Mrs. James Creelman], 1915-1919 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- Creelman, James - Crosby, John (Box 24, Folder 10)
  Creelman, James, 1905-1913
  Cribbs, Christ, 1890
  Criley, John M., 1901-1906
  Crimmins, John D., 1910, 1912
  Crist, Harris M., 1913
  Criswell, R.T., 1916, 1918
  Critchlow, Harrison, 1893
  Crocker, Frank L., 1919
  Crocker, Geo[rge] A., 1894
  Crocker-Wheeler Co. (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1917
  Crockett, E.A., 1915
  Crosby, Fred V.S., 1910
  Crosby, Henrietta [Mrs. S.V.R. Crosby], 1911
  Crosby, John Schuyler, 1912
- Crosby, Stephen - Crutchfield (Box 24, Folder 11)
  Crosby, Stephen V.R., 1907-1917
  Cross and Brown Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1920
  Cross, C.E., 1914
  Crossland, F.W., 1897
  Crossland, Howard R., 1902
  Crow, N., 1900
  Crowninshield, Francis, 1910, 1915
  Crownover, J.C., 1887
  Crucible Club (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1904
  Crucible Steel Company of America (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1901
  Cruikshank Company (New York, N.Y.), 1916
  Crum, A.R., 1900
  Crutcher, Ernest, 1905
  Crutchfield, J.S., 1920
- Cuban - Cummings (Box 24, Folder 12)
  Cuban Orphan Fund [no place], 1899
  Culbertson, B.H., 1901-1910
  Culbertson, Jno. D., 1891
  Culin, Curtis G., Jr., 1919
  Cullinan, J.S., 1902
  Culp, Chas. W., 1896-1899
  Culver, Henry B., 1910-1915
  Cumberland Coal Co. (Baltimore, Md.), 1900
  Cummin, Joseph W., 1902-1903
  Cumming, Alexander, 1917
  Cummings, Amos J., 1894
  Cummings and Co. [no place], 1907
  Cummings, J. Howell, 1902
  Cummings, [?], Mrs., 1915
- Cummins, A., 1901-1916 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Cumont - Currier (Box 25, Folder 2)
  Cumont, Lorenz, 1911
  Cundell, Henry J., 1917-1918
  Cunningham, Clyde Beaumont, 1905, 1916
  Cunningham, Mary H. [Mrs. James Cunningham], 1909
  Cunningham, William Allan, 1916
  Cunz, F.B., 1909
  Curphey, Alfred, 1903, undated
  Current Literature Publishing Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1906
  Current Opinion(New York, N.Y.), 1918
  Currier, A.M., 1909
- Curry, H.M., 1886-1900 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Curry, Margaret - Curtis (Box 25, Folder 4)
  Curry, Margaret, 1908
  Curry, R.M., 1899
  Curtis, F.B.D., 1894
  Curtis, F. Kingsbury, 1910, 1913
  Curtis Francis, 1916
  Curtis, H.D., 1919
  Curtis, Harry A., 1913
  Curtis, Helen R. [Mrs. James F. Curtis], 1911-1912
  Curtis, A.H., Mrs., 1915
  Curtis, O.P., 1916
  Curtis, Ralph, 1906
  Curtis, William E., 1903
- Cushing - Cutting (Box 25, Folder 5)
  Cushing, Edward T., 1893
  Cushing, Marshall, 1890-1915
  Cushman, James Stewart, 1919
  Cutler Manufacturing Co. (Rochester, N.Y.), 1898
  Cutting, R. Fulton, 1907-1913
- Cuyler - Cyrus (Box 25, Folder 6)
  Cuyler, Thomas DeWitt, 1901-1919
  Cyrus, Joseph, 1915
- D. Appleton - Daly (Box 25, Folder 7)
  D. Appleton and Co. (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1901
  D.C. Weeks and Son (New York, N.Y.), 1908
  D. Linehan and Son (Prides Crossing, Mass.), 1907
  D.O. Haynes and Co., Publishers (New York, N.Y.), 1902
  D.S. Hess and Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1890
  D.T. Moore and Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1918
  Dabbs, B.L.H., 1890, 1898
  Daggett, Carrie E., 1909
  Daimler Import Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1911
  Dain, James K., 1887
  Dale, Richard C., 1889-1890
  Dalton, H.G., 1903-1913
  Dalton, Henry R., 1903
  Daly, E.A., 1920
  Daly, Kerfoot W., 1900
  Daly, T.L., 1894, 1904
  Daly, W.H., 1898
- Dalzell - Darlington (Box 25, Folder 8)
  Dalzell, Fisher and Hawkins (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1910
  Dalzell, J. Willis, 1889-1890
  Dalzell, John, 1896-1908
  Dalzell, Thomas K., 1906-1915
  Damrosch, Walter, 1906
  Danehy, Daniel, 1916
  Daniels, Josephus, 1915
  Danker, Daniel J., 1902
  Danner, Geo. H., 1908
  Danz, Mary, 1904
  Darby, George D.B., 1906
  Darby, J. Wm., 1898
  Darlington, H., 1902
- Darr, Luke and Moore [formerly Darr and Moore] (Pittsburgh, Pa. and New York, N.Y.), 1901-1909 (Box 25, Folder 9-12)
- Darr, Luke and Moore (continued), 1910-1913 (Box 26, Folder 1-3)
- Darrach - Dauler (Box 26, Folder 4)
  Darrach, William, 1917
  Darragh, Fannie B. [Mrs. James R. Darragh], 1900
  Darragh, M., 1889
  Darsie, Jas., 1890-1891
  Daub, Theodore G., 1919
  Dauler, Close and Johns (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1911
- Dauphinot - Davis, R.G. (Box 26, Folder 5)
  Dauphinot, G., 1900
  Dau's Blue Books, Inc. (New York, N.Y.), 1915
  Davenport, Butler, 1914
  Davenport, Homer, 1906
  Davenport, Melvin E., 1906
  Davenport, S[amuel] A[rza], 1899
  Davidge, Clara Sedwy [Mrs. Mason C. Davidge], 1911
  Davidson, H.P., 1912, 1915
  Davidson, Robert C., 1897-1917
  Davidson, William A., 1886
  Davidson, William M., 1916
  Davies, John M., 1907
  Davies, Julien T., 1908
  Davies and Company Real Estate (Wilkinsburg, Pa.), 1900
  Davies, Turner and Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1912
  Davis, Arthur B., 1919
  Davis, Ethel A., 1914
  Davis, F.W., Jr., 1913-1914
  Davis, Fred'k W., 1910
  Davis, H.G., 1890
  Davis, Harry, 1908
  Davis, John H., 1907
  Davis, John J., 1900
  Davis, John M., 1894
  Davis, Mrs., 1921
  Davis, R.G., 1890
- Davis, Richard - Davisson (Box 26, Folder 6)
  Davis, Richard C., 1914-1915
  Davis, W.E., 1915
  Davis, W.H., 1891
  Davis, Wm. H., 1909-1914
  Davison, Geo S., 1906
  Davison, H.P., 1916
  Davison, Henry J., 1916
  Davison, Mrs. D.H., 1917
  Davisson and Orr (Clarksburg, W.Va.), 1916
- Dawson - De Forest (Box 26, Folder 7)
  Dawson, J.W., 1905
  Day, Adams and Company (New York, N.Y.), 1911
  Day, Frank Miles, 1907
  Day, William A., 1905-1915
  De Arment, Frank H., 1900
  De Armit, Wm. P., 1897
  De Barros, Louise C., 1909
  De Beruete, A., 1911
  De Bow, T.L., 1894
  De Castes, F.M., 1915
  De Chambrun, Countess, 1915
  De Forest, George, 1904
  De Forest, Robert W., 1909-1919
- De Guichard - De Roy (Box 26, Folder 8)
  De Guichard, Arthur, 1914
  De Haven, Louise R. [Mrs. Hugh De Haven], 1917
  De Kay, Charles, 1903
  De Knight, Clarence W., 1897
  De la Meillaie, Henri, 1912-1913
  De la Porter, Annie, 1915
  De Lamar, Jos. R., 1910
  De Larrea, Miguel, 1916
  De Lewinski, Arnold N., 1908
  De Mier, Jno R., 1917
  De Mot, Jean, 1910
  De Noon, J.C., Mrs., 1914
  De Orueta y Rivero, José, 1916
  De Pew, Chauncey M., 1903
  De Roy, H.D., 1900
- De Saulles - Dean (Box 26, Folder 9)
  De Saulles A.B., 1887-1888
  De Van, W.T., 1919
  De Vaux, N., 1902
  De Vitan, R.G., undated
  De Wild, Carel F.L., 1916-1917, undated
  De Wolfe, Elsie, 1916-1917
  De Wolfe, Tensard, 1909
  De Young, M.H., 1908
  Deacon, Edyth, 1916
  Dean, A.P., 1899
  Dean and Lackey (Ironton, Ohio), 1906
  Dean, Jno., 1897
  Dean, T.B., 1900
- Debarkation - Delavan (Box 26, Folder 10)
  Debarkation Hospital No. 5 [no place], 1919
  Decker, Muriel Richey [Mrs. B.R. Decker], 1902, undated
  Decour, A., 1916
  Deering, Charles, 1901-1916
  Deering, James, 1903
  Degelman and Co. [formerly Degelman and Vogle] (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1905-1916
  Deitrick, James, 1904
  Del Mar, Francesca, 1919
  Del Mar, Walter, 1916, 1919
  Del Sera, Count, 1911-1912
  Delafontaine, P., 1911
  Delamater, G.W., 1891-1903
  Delanoy and Delanoy Insurance (New York, N.Y.), 1901-1907
  Delavan, T.C., 1906-1907
- Delaware - Deming (Box 26, Folder 11)
  Delaware and New England Company (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1889-1891
  Delaware River Steel Casting Company (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1904
  Delaware Water Company (Delaware, Ohio), 1909
  Delineator(New York, N.Y.), 1909
  Dellenbach property on Grant St. (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1909
  Delmonico, L. Crist, 1897
  Demarest, S.E., 1915
  Demarest, W., 1890
  Demarest, Warren H., 1916
  Deming, H.C., 1901-1906
  Deming, L.C., 1906, 1916
- Demuth - Denver (Box 26, Folder 12)
  Demuth, H.C., 1897
  Dengler, Aug, 1901
  Dennis, L.W., 1898
  Dennis, Ruth E., 1916
  Dennis, Samuel S., 1910, 1915
  Denniston, James, 1886
  Denny, Francis H., 1909-1914
  Denny, Mary Speer [Mrs. Francis H. Denny], 1909-1919
  Denver and Salt Lake Railroad Co. (Denver, Col.), 1913
- Derby - Dewey (Box 27, Folder 1)
  Derby, R.C., 1906
  Derby, William P., 1919
  Dermitt, W.V., 1905
  Derrick, Thos. Lee, 1902
  Deschamp, P., 1905
  Després, Georges, 1903-1923
  Desrousseaux, G., 1914
  Detroit Graphite Company [no place], 1913
  Deutsches Journal(New York, N.Y.), 1915
  Devor, William T., 1901
  Dewar and Clinton (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1903, 1913
  Dewar, John, 1887, 1901
  Dewey, C. Frank, 1900
  Dewey, Edward W., 1901
- Dewing - Dill (Box 27, Folder 2)
  Dewing and Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1910
  Dexter, Geo. T., 1907
  Di Campo, Marquis, 1915
  Dice, Margaret, 1894, 1899
  Dick Brothers and Co. (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1891, 1908
  Dick, M.M., 1890
  Dick, Saml. B., 1896
  Dick Press (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1911
  Dickey, John N., 1909-1910
  Dickie, J.F., 1901
  Dickson, Saml., 1886
  Diedrich, N., 1884
  Diehl, W.J., 1904
  Dielman, Frederick, 1906
  Dietz, C.N., 1898
  Dill, Arthur C.. 1916
  Dill, James B., 1900
  Dill, M. Reese, 1885
- Diller - Dimock (Box 27, Folder 3)
  Diller, Theodore, 1906, 1916
  Dillistin, H.P., 1916
  Dillon, P.R., 1892, 1899, 1915
  Dilworth, DeWitt, 1887, 1906, 1908
  Dilworth, L.L., 1903
  Dilworth, Lawrence, 1907, 1911
  Dimock, Geo. E., 1913
  Dimock, Susan Whitney [Mrs. Henry F. Dimock], 1910-1912
- Dinkelspiel - Dixon (Box 27, Folder 4)
  Dinkelspiel Wm., 1886, 1888
  Dinkey, A.C., 1906, 1914
  Dinkey, C.E., 1913
  Dinklage, A., 1900
  Diocese of Pittsburgh [Pittsburgh, Pa.], 1916-1917
  Distributing and Importing Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1914
  Ditson, Alice M. [Mrs. Charles H. Ditson], 1906, 1909
  Dixon, C.H., 1906
  Dixon, Frances S., 1912
  Dixon, George D., 1917-1918
- Doan - Dole (Box 27, Folder 5)
  Doan, Robert E., 1911
  Doar, Rosa, 1900
  Dodd, Frank N., 1916
  Dodge, Arthur M., 1915
  Dodge, Cleveland H., 1917
  Dodge, Elizabeth W., 1915
  Dodge, M. Hartley, 1903
  Doerr, Geo., 1900
  Doerr, Josephine B., 1905
  Doerr, Mary Ann [Mrs. George Doerr], 1906-1907
  Doerr, William H., 1912
  Dolan, Pat., 1902
  Dolan, Thomas, 1906
  Dole, Nathan Haskell, 1911-1912
- Dom - Donnelly (Box 27, Folder 6)
  Dom, William T., Jr., 1915
  Dominick, Bayard, 1915
  Donohoe, T.J., 1897
  Donahue, John Vincent, 1916-1917
  Donegal Oil Co. ([?], W.Va.), 1900
  Donegan, James S., 1908
  Donkin, Wm. S., 1915
  Donlon, Thomas James, 1908
  Donnell, James J., 1903, 1907
  Donnelly, Chas., 1889, 1892
- Donner, William H., 1902-1922 (Box 27, Folder 7-12)
- Donon - Dow (Box 28, Folder 1)
  Donon, Joseph, 1917
  Donovan, James P., 1921
  Dorchester, Mary H., [1904?]
  Dornheim, H.E., 1918
  Dorrington, F.C., 1899
  Dotson, N.B., 1910
  Doty, L.B., 1891
  Doty, M.M., 1910
  Doubleday Page and Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1909
  Dougherty, Wm., 1916
  Douglas, Isabel R., 1909
  Douglas, R. Langton, 1909
  Douglas, Saml. B., 1900-1907
  Doussan, T., 1915
  Dow, Jones and Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1902-1916
- Dowdeswell - Du Barry (Box 28, Folder 2)
  Dowdeswell, Charles, 1900
  Down Town Association (New York, N.Y.), 1891, 1899
  Downing, Dwight F., 1886
  Downing, Henry F., 1919
  Doyle, John, 1918
  Drais, Clara C., 1909-1911
  Drake, Tracy C., 1908
  Drant, Emma, 1907
  Drape, Jas. W., 1897
  Dravo, Edward E., 1912
  Dravo, John F., 1890, 1897
  Dreicer and Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1913-1916
  Dreiser, Theodore, 1909
  Dresel, Ellis Loring, 1910-1918
  Drew and Sons (London, England), 1899
  Drexel and Co. Bankers (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1887-1907
  Drill, J.M, 1894-1916
  Du Barry, J[oseph] N., 1887
- Du Bois - Duniway (Box 28, Folder 3)
  Du Bois, A.J., 1910
  Du Pont, Coleman, 1918
  Du Puy, Herbert, 1899-1919
  Du Shane, J.M., 1900
  Du Shane, Mary E., 1903, 1909
  Du Val, C. Raoul, 1906
  Du Val, Horace C., 1907
  Duane, Morris, Heckscher and Robert (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1906
  Dudley, James L., 1903
  Dudley, Jos., 1912
  Duenkel, Adolph, 1905
  Duff, H.K., 1917, 1921
  Duff, Harriet, 1904
  Duff, J. Boyd, 1890, 1909
  Dulfer, I.W., 1893
  Duluth, Missabe and Northern Railway Co. [no place], 1904
  Dumbauld, D.W.C., 1896
  Dumm, C.E., 1894
  Dummett, Arthur, 1920
  Dunbar Township High School (Connellsville, Pa.), 1914
  Dunham, Wm. R., 1889
  Duniway, C.A., 1895-1900
- Dunlevey - Dunn, James (Box 28, Folder 4)
  Dunlevey, Helen, 1906
  Dunlap, John R., 1901
  Dunn, James H., 1912-1918
- Dunn, John - Duquesne (Box 28, Folder 5)
  Dunn, John E., 1909, 1917
  Dunn, Louise K., 1916
  Dunne, Finley Peter, 1918
  Dunnell, Henry N., 1911
  Dunning, A.W., 1910
  Duparquet Huot and Moneuse Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1902
  Duquesne Chemical Mfg. Co. (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1913
  Duquesne Club (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1886, 1919
  Duquesne Land Co. (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1888
  Duquesne Light Co. [Pittsburgh, Pa.], 1917
  Duquesne National Bank (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1902-1920
- Durand - Dustin, Alfred (Box 28, Folder 6)
  Durand-Ruel Galleries (New York, N.Y.), 1897-1898, 1912
  Durkin, Edward Lawrence, 1912
  Durning, Charles, 1917
  Durr, Josephine, 1896
  Duryea and Potter (New York, N.Y.), 1903
  Dusenberry, L.H., 1888
  Dustin, Alfred A., 1916
- Dustin, Alton C., 1901-1907 (Box 28, Folder 7-11)
- Dustin, Alton C. (continued), 1907-1921 (Box 29, Folder 1-4)
- Dutton - Duvall (Box 29, Folder 5)
  Dutton, Alice M., 1910[?]
  Duvall, W.C., 1903
- Duveen Bros. (New York, N.Y.), 1906-1921 (Box 29, Folder 6-9)
- Dvorak - E.V. Brokaw (Box 29, Folder 10)
  Dvorak, J.F., 1916
  Dwight and Chandler, Architects (Boston, Mass.), 1901
  Dysart, J.C., 1888
  E.A. Harris and Co. (Victoria, B.C.), 1919
  E.A. Williams and Son (Jersey City, N.J.), 1896
  E.B. Latham and Company (New York, N.Y.), 1920
  E.C. Miller and Co. [no place], 1906
  E. Gimpel and Wildenstein (New York, N.Y.), 1915
  E.H. Gay and Co. (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1906
  E. Lamontagne and Sons (New York, N.Y.), 1893
  E.M. Todd Co. (Smithfield, Va.), 1900-1902
  E.P. Dutton and Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1909-1918
  E.R. Chapman and Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1907
  E.R. Grabow and Co. (Swampscott, Mass.), 1912
  E.V. Brokaw and Bro. (New York, N.Y.), 1918
- Eagland - Eberts (Box 29, Folder 11)
  Eagland and Co, [London, England?], 1903
  Ealy, Taylor F., 1893
  Eames, A.H., 1910
  Eames, J., 1906
  Easley, Dan, 1896
  East Chicago Co. (Chicago, Ill.), 1902-1913
  East End Cadets, East End Christian Church (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1912
  East End Dramatic Club [Pittsburgh, Pa.], 1890
  East End Electric Light Co. (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1888-1893
  East End Gas Co. (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1887
  East End Hospital (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1900-1901
  East End Savings and Trust Co. (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1909
  Easton, Susan R. (Mrs. F.C. Easton), 1902
  Eaton, D.C., 1899
  Eaton, H.B., 1915
  Eaton, Seymour, 1905
  Eaton, W.H., 1899
  Eberhart, A.O., 1918
  Eberts, J.M, Mrs., 1908
- Eckels - Edie (Box 30, Folder 1)
  Eckels, James H., 1906-1907
  Ecker, H.P., 1901-1902
  Economic Club of New York (New York, N.Y.), 1908, 1915
  Eddy, Robt. E., 1898
  Edenborn Wm., 1905
  Edgar, L.E., Mrs., 1903
  Edie, Lilly B. (Mrs. Wm. A. Edie), 1909
- Edinger - Edwards (Box 30, Folder 2)
  Edinger, O.H., 1907
  Edison General Electric Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1892-1893
  Edmonds, Richard H., 1906-1917
  Edmunds, Frank W., 1903
  Edsall, R.E., 1899
  Edward F. Caldwell and Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1906, 1909
  Edward G. Roberts and Company (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1915
  Edward, Geo. D., 1907
  Edward Sweet and Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1912, 1914
  Edwards and Bryan (New York, N.Y.), 1908
  Edwards, Andrew S., 1907
  Edwards, B.I., 1906
  Edwards, Cyrus, 1907
  Edwards, D.R., 1909
  Edwards, Dwight W., 1918
  Edwards, Ogden M., 1901
- Egan - Elder (Box 30, Folder 3)
  Egan, W.H., 1919
  Ehrich, H.L., 1915
  Ehrich, Louis R., 1908-1911
  Eichbaum Lithographing and Printing Co. (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1903
  Eicher, Thos. D., 1886
  Eichleay, John, Jr., 1901, 1912
  Eidgenössische Bank (Zürich, Switzerland), 1899
  Eiler, Edw., 1890
  Eilman, M.G.F. (Mrs. Bradley Eilman), 1916
  Eisenhuth, John W., 1901
  Elder, Cyrus, 1889, 1891
  Elder, J.F., 1901
- Elias - Eltonhead (Box 30, Folder 4)
  Elias, Isabella H., 1914
  Eliot, Amory, 1909
  Eliot, Charles W., 1908, 1917
  Elkins, S[tephen] B[enton], 1897-1902
  Elkins, William L., Jr., 1901
  Elkins, Morris and Co. [no place], 1921
  Ellman, Lawrence B., 1917
  Ellis, David A., 1908
  Ellis, Rudolph, 1899, 1913
  Ellis, W.H., 1916, 1918
  Ellis, William [S.?], 1902
  Ellsworth, J.S., 1918
  Ellsworth, James W., 1887, 1906
  Ellsworth Steam Laundry, Dye House, and Bath Rooms (Ellsworth, Me.), 1886
  Ellwood, I.L., 1897
  Elmore, James, 1904-1912
  Elmore, Susan, 1915
  Elmore, W.A., 1918
  Eltonhead, E.Y., 1911
  Eltonhead, Marion T., 1911
- Ely - English, George (Box 30, Folder 5)
  Ely, Alfred, Mrs., 1916
  Ely, Arthur C., 1891
  Ely, D.B., 1907
  Ely, Robert Erskine, 1908-1913
  Ely, Theo. N., 1906
  Emerson, Alfred, 1916
  Emerson, Wm. R.P., 1919
  Emery, Dean, 1909
  Emery, Henry C., 1910
  Emery, Henry C., Mrs., 1919
  Emmet, B.H., 1914
  Emmett, John, 1911
  Emmons, H.E., 1902
  Empire Coal Lands [no place,] 1914-1918
  Employers' Liability Assurance Corp., Ltd. (London, England), 1920, 1922
  Encyclopedia Americana Corp. (New York, N.Y.), 1916
  Endicott, Clara T., 1907
  Endicott, William C., 1919
  Enell, George A., 1902-1913
  Engelsman, A.D., 1906
  Engineering and Mining Journal(New York, N.Y.), 1891
  Engineering Magazine(London, England), 1905
  Engineers' Club (New York, N.Y.), 1899-1900
  Engineers' Society of Western Pennsylvania (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1901
  English, George W., 1897
- English, H.D.W., 1897-1918 (Box 30, Folder 6)
- English, H.D.W., Mrs. - Epping (Box 30, Folder 7)
  English, H.D.W., Mrs., 1908
  English, John E., 1894, 1897
  English, Mary C., 1893-1897
  English, W.Y., 1911
  Eno, Amos F., 1890-1895
  Enright, R.E., 1919
  Episcopal Church Home (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1903
  Epping-Carpenter Co. (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1909
- Equitable Life - Equitable Trust (Box 30, Folder 8)
  Equitable Life Assurance Society (New York, N.Y., and Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1897-1920
  Equitable Trust Company of New York (New York, N.Y.), 1902-1910
- Erdman - Ertell (Box 30, Folder 9)
  Erdman, H.C., 1908
  Erdody, Leowald, 1916
  Erie Railroad Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1909-1922
  Ernst, Eugene C.F., 1909
  Erskine, Albert DeWolf, [1896?], 1901-1913
  Ertell, W.H., 1886
- Escher - Estopinal (Box 30, Folder 10)
  Escher, B.E., 1911
  Esser, John A., 1910
  Essex County Associated Boards of Trade (Lynn, Mass.), 1911-1915
  Essex County Club (Manchester, Mass.), 1902-1925
  Essex County Co-Operative Farming Association (Topsfield, Mass.), 1922
  Estate Stove Co. (Hamilton, Ohio), 1911
  Estes, Clifford N., 1916
  Estopinal, Leonidas B., 1917
- Etowah - Everson (Box 30, Folder 11)
  Etowah Iron Co. (Cartersville, Ga.), 1890
  Eugenie [firm] (New York, N.Y.), 1912
  Eureka Consolidated Mining Co. (San Francisco, Cal.), 1887-1889
  Eureka Fire Brick Co. (Mt. Braddock, Pa.), 1890
  Eustis, [?],Mrs., 1917
  Euwer[?], Anthony H., 1903
  Evans, Amelia C., 1901
  Evans, Charles, Jr., 1912-1915
  Evans, Frederick, 1902
  Evans, T.D., 1898
  Evans, Wm. (heirs of), 1904
  Evening Mail(New York, N.Y.), 1916
  Evening Post(New York, N.Y.), 1902-1908
  Everett, Edward, 1906
  Everson, John L., 1898
- Ewart - Eyre (Box 30, Folder 12)
  Ewart, Richard H., 1912, 1915
  Ewing, Jno. K., 1889-1892
  Ewing, Jno. K., Jr., 1903
  Ewing, Nathaniel, 1897-1899
  Ewing, S.E., 1890-1891, undated
  Excelsior Express and Standard Cab Co. (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1903
  Exchange Bank (Beaver Falls, Pa.), 1893
  Exchange National Bank (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1890
  Export Shipping Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1903
  Eyermann, Peter, 1907
  Eyre, John R., 1915
- F.B. Vandergrift - Fanshawe (Box 31, Folder 1)
  F.B. Vandergrift and Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1897-1900
  F.G. Conley and Co. (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1909
  F.H. Prince and Co. (Boston, Mass.), 1907-1912
  F. Kleinberger Galleries (New York, N.Y.), 1909, 1917
  F. Sander and Co. (St. Albans, [England]), 1899
  Fagan, A. Florence, 1902
  Fagans, Philip D., 1917
  Fahnestock, Wm., 1908
  Fairbanks Co. (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1903
  Fairbairn, Andrew, 1896
  Fairchild, B. Tappen, 1917
  Fairchild, S.R., 1913
  Fairfax, John, 1901
  Falkenan, Victor, 1907-1913
  Fallet, C., 1893
  Fancher, F.T., 1908
  Fankhauser, Charles K., 1918
  Fanshawe, W.S., 1906
- Farabee - Faraday (Box 31, Folder 2)
  Farabee, W.C., 1902
  Faraday Coal and Coke Co. (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1906-1923
- Farjeon, Bagot and Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1905-1915 (Box 31, Folder 3-4)
- Farland - Fayette (Box 31, Folder 5)
  Farland, J.T., 1890
  Farmer, C.W., 1904
  Farmer, Edwin, 1917
  Farmers Loan and Trust Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1895-1906
  Farmington Society (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1906
  Farquhar, A.B., 1894-1911
  Farr, Frances (Mrs. John Farr), 1918
  Farrand, Wilson, 1918
  Farrell, A.J., 1918
  Farrell, J.A., 1908
  Farrell, James A., 1917
  Farren, C.F., 1901
  Farrer, Jacques F., 1922
  Farrer, Patrick, 1915
  Farwell, Catherine E., 1912
  Faure, John P., 1912
  Fay, John W., 1916
  Fayerweather, W.O., 1892
  Fayette County Bar Committee (Uniontown, Pa.), 1907
  Fayette County Commissioners' Office (Uniontown, Pa.), 1898
- Fearon - Feltwell (Box 31, Folder 6)
  Fearon, Walter P., 1915
  Fechtig, St. George, 1915
  Federal Book Concern (New York, N.Y.), 1899-1900
  Federal Real Estate Board (Washington, D.C.), 1922
  Federal Reserve Bank of New York (New York, N.Y.), 1923
  Federal Reserve Board (Washington, D.C.), 1916
  Federal Steel Foundry Co. (Chester, Pa.), 1913-1918
  Federal Trade Information Service (Washington, D.C.), 1919
  Felician Sisters (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1919
  Fellowes, Charles, 1915
  Fellowship Club (Philadelphia, Pa.), 10 Dec [no year]
  Felton, E.C., 1893-1909
  Felton, S.M., 1893-1894
  Feltwell, Sophy E., 1889
- Fenn - Ferguson, John (Box 31, Folder 7)
  Fenn, James V., 1889
  Fenner, Saml. C., 1908
  Fenning, John, 1916
  Ferguson, E.M, 1886-1906
  Ferguson, Helen, 1910
  Ferguson, Henry, 1912
  Ferguson, John M., 1906
- Ferguson, Walton, 1885-1915 (Box 31, Folder 8-9)
- Ferguson, Walton, Jr. - Fidelity (Box 31, Folder 10)
  Ferguson, Walton, Jr., 1915
  Ferguson, Wm. Russell, 1898
  Ferro-Carril Mexicano ([?], Mexico), 1892
  Fessenden, Reginald A., 1911
  Fidelity and Casualty Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1904
  Fidelity Appraisal Co. (Milwaukee, Wis.), 1916
  Fidelity Insurance, Trust and Safe Deposit Co. (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1898-1901
  Fidelity Title and Trust Co. (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1888-1898
- Fidelity Title and Trust Co. (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1899-1922 (Box 31, Folder 11-12)
- Field -Figaro (Box 31, Folder 13)
  Field, Henry M., 1896
  Field, Marshall, 1897-1905
  Field, Wm. B. Osgood, 1909-1910
  Fifth Avenue Association (New York, N.Y.), 1914-1919
  Fifth Avenue Bank (New York, N.Y.), 1905-1916
  Fifth Av. Pres. Ch. Project [?], [no place], 1886
  Figaro, Huret, 1903
  Figaro(Paris, France), 1903, 1910
- Filbert - First National Bank, Columbus, Ohio (Box 32, Folder 1)
  Filbert, G.H., 1909
  Filbert, W.J., 1915-1916
  Fimmermon, Sam'l. G., 1909
  Financial Directory Association (New York, N.Y.), 1903
  Financial Encyclopaedia(New York, N.Y.), 1909
  Finch, J.A., 1899
  Finch, John A., 1905
  Findley, John P., 1917, 1919
  Finelli, Joseph, 1902
  Finley, J.B., 1916
  Finley, John Card, 1918
  Finley, John H., 1912
  Finley, W.W., 1913
  Finnegan, P.W., 1898
  Finney, R., 1904
  Fireproofine Manufacturing Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1901
  First M.E. Church (Monaca, Pa.), 1909
  First National Bank (Columbus, Ohio), 1899
- First National Bank (Connellsville, Pa.) - First National Bank (Mt. Pleasant, Pa..) (Box 32, Folder 2)
  First National Bank (Connellsville, Pa.), 1885-1894
  First National Bank (Mt. Pleasant, Pa.), 1887-1895
- First National Bank (New York, N.Y.), 1901-1924 (Box 32, Folder 3-4)
- First National Bank (Pittsburgh, Pa.) - Fish (Box 32, Folder 5)
  First National Bank (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1908
  First National Bank (Scottdale, Pa.), 1889-1893
  First National Bank (Sewickley, Pa.), 1891
  First National Bank (Stamford, Conn.), 1887-1888